[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "Sixteen kilometers is _____ the same as ten miles.",
        "answer": "roughly"
    },
    {
        "question": "This type of butterfly lives in a forest _____.",
        "answer": "habitat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whenever there is a period of bad events, people often call it an _____.",
        "answer": "apocalypse"
    },
    {
        "question": "My teacher worries that we are not doing enough to _____ the environment for future generations.",
        "answer": "protect"
    },
    {
        "question": "My mother sold all of her stocks as soon as the stock market started to _____.",
        "answer": "decline"
    },
    {
        "question": "I tied my shoes very tightly, and now I can't _____ the knot!",
        "answer": "undo"
    },
    {
        "question": "All of the different animals on Earth are important, so we need to ____ them — even the ugly ones!",
        "answer": "protect"
    },
    {
        "question": "It’s very difficult to _____ bad grammar habits without a lot of practice.",
        "answer": "undo"
    },
    {
        "question": "The forest was recently named a firefly _____ area, so you can’t go in without permission.",
        "answer": "conservation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lancheng Bed and Breakfast offers guests _____ tours of the local area.",
        "answer": "ecological"
    },
    {
        "question": "The president is very popular among his _____ supporters.",
        "answer": "grassroots"
    },
    {
        "question": "I can’t believe my father is in the forest _____ his own Christmas tree this year.",
        "answer": "harvesting"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you study English a little bit each day, you will _____ improve.",
        "answer": "steadily"
    },
    {
        "question": "Be careful with those butterfly wings — they’re very _____.",
        "answer": "delicate"
    },
    {
        "question": "The book provided a very basic plan for _____ organizations to help save the logical environment.",
        "answer": "grassroots"
    },
    {
        "question": "Farmers have to work hard to keep _____ insects out of their crops.",
        "answer": "invasive"
    },
    {
        "question": "We can make ourselves happier once we have the _____ of what we really want in our lives.",
        "answer": "consciousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "Scientists often _____ the effects of climate change in their reports.",
        "answer": "note"
    },
    {
        "question": "Since coming to college, I’ve noticed that I’ve _____ been gaining weight.",
        "answer": "steadily"
    },
    {
        "question": "The _____ effects of the new airport need to be studied before it can be built.",
        "answer": "ecological"
    },
    {
        "question": "It’s a _____ fact that not getting enough sleep affects your memory.",
        "answer": "well-known"
    },
    {
        "question": "There is no way I am _____ for your break-up with your girlfriend. I only talked to her once!",
        "answer": "to blame"
    },
    {
        "question": "We need to have stronger laws to limit the _____ of polluting gases, such as carbon dioxide.",
        "answer": "emission"
    },
    {
        "question": "Red skies at sunset often _____ an approaching typhoon.",
        "answer": "indicate"
    },
    {
        "question": "Many people think a world war would cause an _____ for life on Earth.",
        "answer": "apocalypse"
    },
    {
        "question": "I put my finger right through the paper — I didn’t realize how _____ it was.",
        "answer": "delicate"
    },
    {
        "question": "Our teacher taught us that diamonds are actually _____ crystals.",
        "answer": "carbon"
    },
    {
        "question": "The professor was _____ for her ability to make difficult subjects easy to understand.",
        "answer": "well-known"
    },
    {
        "question": "Covid-19 was _____ for the loss of tourism in the beach resort.",
        "answer": "to blame"
    },
    {
        "question": "You recent study habits _____ that you are taking this course very seriously.",
        "answer": "indicate"
    },
    {
        "question": "Taiwan’s birth rate has been on the _____ for several years now.",
        "answer": "decline"
    },
    {
        "question": "City traffic is a large cause of _____ pollution.",
        "answer": "carbon"
    },
    {
        "question": "We all left the meeting at _____ the same time.",
        "answer": "roughly"
    },
    {
        "question": "The children enjoyed _____ their own pumpkins for Halloween.",
        "answer": "harvesting"
    },
    { "question": "Please _____ my new telephone number.", "answer": "note" }
]